[Music]
epic events the cool people behind the
successful OPM music fest would like to
proudly announce that for this year our
or Music Festival we have found the
perfect partner who's all about changing
the way people feel about insurance and
celebrating its death year in the
Philippines that is FWB life insurance
I really most uh excited about to share
with you today is that we created the
first ever insurance for music
lovers if you purchase the plan it gives
you an access for free to Orange ticket
orang ticket
[Music]
benefit yes Jay and
Louie the challenge to make aora 10x
more exciting from music lovers is
officially
[Applause]
[Music]
accepted